{
    "id": "0fe6c777ac6c40239b6afce008c4b0c8",
    "title": "Modal Auxiliaries Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She ....................... have gone to work but I am not sure.",
            "description": "Can is only used to talk about theoretical possibility. In other cases, we use may to indicate possibility. ",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "can",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ad6e6a7138b54ea18565eabc8ac3879b"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ............................ be right. I don't know.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "can",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2039e2d673574ec3bd6195d33a9ebe4a"
        },
        {
            "question": "........................... I borrow your camera?",
            "description": "Both can and may are used to ask for permission. ",
            "answers": [
                "Can",
                "May",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "60659343cf134e17aee593fdb28c9fad"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................ you move a bit?",
            "description": "In polite requests, we use can, not may.",
            "answers": [
                "Can",
                "May",
                "Might"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2c6d5cf8d6414aa3bf7cc0fc7b776544"
        },
        {
            "question": "...................... I come in teacher?",
            "description": "Both can and may can be used to ask for permission. ",
            "answers": [
                "May",
                "Can",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3c04d69de66b4f32996b539e9581dcb6"
        },
        {
            "question": "She .......................... read when she was just three.",
            "description": "We use could to talk about past ability. ",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could",
                "might"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0264a5ffe2984b0ebaeb1bfecab3827d"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is impossible. They ............................. have lost their way.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can't",
                "mayn't",
                "mustn't"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8d8e0f5b893c4fcda46839f8fb63a30a"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ....................... go after you have finished your work.",
            "description": "May is considered more correct here but can is gaining acceptance. ",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "can",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1485b1dd8fab439db6b25e56bdf9183f"
        },
        {
            "question": "What ......................... you do if she doesn't recognize you?",
            "description": "To express simple futurity, we use will. ",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "will",
                "shall"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e9114f6e91234276845003441aece179"
        },
        {
            "question": ".............................. you translate this article into German?",
            "description": "Both can and could are possible here could is used in a more polite style. ",
            "answers": [
                "Can",
                "May",
                "Could",
                "Either can or could"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "a1d89852ab674abe9c2e34ce90132aa9"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who ......................... it be?",
            "description": "In questions we use can to express possibility. ",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "may",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ee6661bf67664e7cb1fd8c07a04e28bd"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ................... smoke in the kitchen.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "might not",
                "cannot",
                "could not"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a35df017691f42948c35523c4c3c05fa"
        }
    ]
}